

Md. Rohul Amin

Software Engineer

 ♦ Sha 66/3, Shadhinata Sarani, North Badda, Gulshan, Dhaka, Bangladesh
 ## 05 Jan 1996

■ Bangladeshi @ Unmarried in radipu ♠ radipu ♠ radipu
♠ radipu.me ♠ radipu

CAREER OBJECTIVES

I am experienced in leadership and both front-end and back-end programming languages. Now, I am looking for establishing my career as a .NET developer and team lead. I am a quick learner and willing to learn new technologies to upgrade myself with time. I am working with .NET technology since 2018.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Aug 2022 – present

Software Developer

Dhaka, Bangladesh

Gulf State Software □

- · Working in Warehouse Management System.
- Adding new features and debugging.
- Technologies: C# ASP.NET, JSON, Azure DevOps, MSSQL Server, Angular

Jan 2022 – Jul 2022

Software Engineer

Dhaka, Bangladesh

CureTech Ltd 🛮

- Developed web applications.
- · Worked on the Engineering part for different projects.
- Lead a team.
- Technologies: C# .NET5, Angular, NodeJS, MSSQL, Laravel, MySQL, AWS, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Software Design

Aug 2021 – Jan 2022 Sunderland, England

Software Engineer

Ginilab Limited

- Worked on Restaurant Management System.
- Added new features, and debugging.
- Technologies: .NET Framework, DevExpress, WinForms, Software Design, Fron-end, and Back-end.

Feb 2021 - Jul 2021

Software Engineer

Dhaka, Bangladesh

OurEdu

- Worked on Account Management System.
- Upgrading the old technology to new technology.
- Technologies: C# ASP.NET Core 3.1, JavaScript, Bootstrap, jQuery, LINQ, CSS, MSSQL, and DevOps.

Jan 2015 – Jan 2021 Dhaka, Bangladesh

Head of Information and Communication Technology

Bangladesh Study Forum (BDSF)

- I developed the whole IT system for this organization.
- Lead the IT team
- What have I done: Website development, Organized programs, public speaking, Leadership.

PROJECTS

Aug 2022 - present

Amedig Management 🛮

Warehouse Management

• Technologie: Azure DevOps, .NET Framework, MSSQL Server, Angular

Feb 2022 - Jul 2022

Bachao 🛮

Against the rape

- It's a mobile application platform against rape.
- The backend was developed with .NET.
- Technologies: .NET5, Angular, WebAPI, MSSQL

Aug 2021 - Jan 2022

Restaurant Management System

- It's a desktop software, mostly used in the UK and in the middle east.
- Nearly 200+ restaurants and thousands of customers use this software for ordering food inside and outside the restaurant.
- Added new features and debugging.
- Technologies: ASP.NET, DevExpress, WinForms, MySQL, Laragon, HeidiSQL

Feb 2021 - May 2021

Account Management System for Shidlai Ashraf Secondary School

- Enroll new students with details information.
- · Adding new staff and teachers.
- Payroll and tuition fees management.
- Online payment module.
- Technologies: C#, ASP.NET Core 3.1, JavaScript, Bootstrap, CSS, jQuery, JSON, LINQ, and following Onion Architecture.

May 2019 - Aug 2019

Library Management System

Technologies: C#, ASP.NET Core 2.1, Bootstrap, CSS, jQuery, JSON, LINQ.

SKILLS

Programming Language

C, C++, Java, JavaScript, C#, R, Python, TypeScript

Backend

.NET Core, .NET, NodeJS, Laravel

DevOps

AWS, GCP, Azure, Docker, Jenkins, Kubernetes, Bash

Data Structure and Algorithm

Cyber Security

Penetration, Forensics, Reverse Engineering, Social Engineering Frontend

VueJS, Angular, HTML5, Bootstrap, CSS3, Sass

Database

Oracle, MySQL, MSSQL Server, PostgreSQL

Source Control

Git, GitHub

Interpersonal skills •

Listening, Caring, Leadership, Self-Motivated, Responsibility, Teamwork

EDUCATION

May 2021 Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and Engineering

Dhaka, Bangladesh International University of Business Agriculture and Technology

Completed BSc with a CGPA of 3.27 out of 4.00

Jul 2011 - Aug 2013 Higher Secondary Certificate

Dhaka, Bangladesh Cambrian College

Completed HSC with a GPA of 5.00 out of 5.00

Jan 2009 - May 2011 Secondary School Certificate

Cumilla, Bangladesh Shidlai Ashraf Secondary School

Completed SSC with a GPA of 5.00 out of 5.00

Learning New Skills

· Public Speaking

Reading

Writing

Leadership

LANGUAGES

Bangla • • • • • English • • • •